Bell Brothers Collection
Bell Brothers Collection
1910-1963
Bell Music Box
1500 items
Collection consists of non-commercial recordings on 78RPM, 45RPM, and 33RPM phonograph records and 1/4 inch audio tapes.
4551514
Biographical History
Joseph and Max Bell established the Bell Music Box record shop in Manhattan, New York City following World War II. The brothers were Russian immigrants, who spent time in Cuba before coming to America. While in Cuba, they took an interest in Spanish language recordings as well as the music of the Caribbean. Their store was known to record aficionados and collectors nationwide and was comprehensive in its breadth -- if they did not have a copy of a particular recording, they would make their own. As a result, their inventory contained both commercially produced and sold recordings, and personal copies made for their own reference and use.
In 1963, Syracuse University purchased the entire inventory of the Bell Brothers' store. Commercial recordings were integrated into the
Belfer Commercial Phonograph Disc Recordings
. Latin American and Caribbean recordings were separated into the
Bell Brothers Collection of Latin American and Caribbean Recordings
. Noncommercial recordings were retained as the
Bell Brothers Collection
.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Bell Brothers Collection consists of instantaneous disc recordings, many of them transcriptions of radio broadcasts, as well as dubbed copies of commercial releases made on site at the Bell Music Box. For ease of locating a specific title, the inventory below lists items alphabetically by title, though they are not physically arranged in this order.
Arrangement of the Collection
Arranged by format. Within that, items are physically arranged sequentially by ID number.
Related Material
See also the
Belfer Commercial Phonograph Disc Collection
and the
Bell Brothers Collection of Latin American and Caribbean Recordings
.
Separated Material
Commercial recordings were integrated into the
Belfer Commercial Phonograph Disc Recordings
. Latin American and Caribbean recordings were separated into the
Bell Brothers Collection of Latin American and Caribbean Recordings
.
Subject and Genre Headings
Music; Popular culture; Bell Brothers Records.; Jazz -- United States.; Popular music -- United States -- 20th century.; Radio broadcasting.; Radio advertising.; 45 rpm records.; 78 rpm records.; Audiotapes.; Long-playing records.; Phonograph records.; Sound recordings.
Acquisition Information
Purchase, 1963.
Inventory
- Phonograph records
  - 1. Eno Of Liebeslieder; 2. Ropartz: Pastorale and Dance, for Oboe and Orchestra, Wallenstein; No. 5: Liebeslieder, Music Guild, (Disc 2 of 3), undated; bell_brothers_195; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - 1. Liebeslieder; 2. Ropartz: Pastorale and Dance, for Oboe and Orchestra, Wallenstein; No. 3: Liebeslieder, Music Guild, (Disc 3 of 3), undated; bell_brothers_196; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - 1013: Kansas City Caboose; 1015: Helena’s Dream, undated; bell_brothers_143; lacquer on glass disc
  - 2nd Rhapsody, Special Recording, George Gershwin, conductor, 06/26/1931; 07/19/1956; bell_brothers_449; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - A Holiday Album of Music featuring The U. S. Army Band and Chorus, conducted by Major Hugh Curry with music designed especially for New Year’s Day and Lincoln's Birthday (No. 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_566; vinyl disc
  - A Holiday Album of Music featuring The U. S. Army Band and Chorus, conducted by Major Hugh Curry with music designed especially for Washington's Birthday and Easter (No. 3-4), undated; bell_brothers_567; vinyl disc
  - A Holiday Album of Music featuring The U. S. Army Band and Chorus, conducted by Major Hugh Curry with music designed especially for Memorial Day and Independence Day (No. 5-6), undated; bell_brothers_532; vinyl disc
  - A Holiday Album of Music featuring The U. S. Army Band and Chorus, conducted by Major Hugh Curry with music designed especially for Labor Day (No. 7), undated; bell_brothers_533; vinyl disc
  - A Touch Of Venus (Part 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_003; acetate on aluminum disc
  - Abbott and Costello, replacing Comedy Caravan (No. 74), 11/09/1944; bell_brothers_466; vinyl disc
  - ACS: 1958 Cancer Crusade half-hour variety program (No. 5), bell_brothers_793; vinyl disc
  - Agnus Dei, Le Deo Gratias, Jesus Dulcis, Pius X School, undated; bell_brothers_257; shellac disc
  - AHA: Heart Sunday Announcements, 02/13/1955; 02/20/1955; bell_brothers_794; vinyl disc
  - AHA: Heart Sunday Program: Heart Sunday Program, Heart Sunday House Party; AHA: Heart Sunday Announcements, 02/17/1958; 02/28/1958; bell_brothers_795; vinyl disc
  - Al Verde Limon; Ole Docores, undated; bell_brothers_101; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Alabama Jug Band; Cuarteto Caney, undated; bell_brothers_069; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Albert Stoessel: Concerto Grosso (Parts 1 and 3), 05/11/1938; bell_brothers_159; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Albert Stoessel: Concerto Grosso (Parts 2 and 4), 05/11/1938; bell_brothers_160; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Albert Stoessel: Concerto Grosso (Parts 5 and 7), 05/11/1938; bell_brothers_161; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Anchors Aweigh (Film), (Parts 3 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_234; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Anibal Troilo: Farolito De Papel, tango; Uno, tango, undated; bell_brothers_098; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Antonio Vargas Heredia, Will Glahe, (J. M. Merenciano); Tango Espagnola (M. Fischer), Will Glahe, undated; bell_brothers_119; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - At Ease (No. 76), undated; bell_brothers_512; vinyl disc
  - Augustin Magaldi; The Spaniels; The Moonglows, Red Holloway’s Orchestra; The Flamingos, undated; bell_brothers_059; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Ay Monang; Pakiskis, undated; bell_brothers_076; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 1, undated; bell_brothers_235; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 2 (1st Session), undated; bell_brothers_236; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 3 (1st Session), undated; bell_brothers_237; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 4, undated; bell_brothers_238; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 5 (1st Session), undated; bell_brothers_239; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 6 (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_240; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 6 (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_242; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 7, undated; bell_brothers_241; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 8, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_243; shellac disc
  - Bach: Art of the Fugue, E. Power Biggs, Contra # 8, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_244; shellac disc
  - Bach: Chorale [sic] Prelude - Ich Ruf Zu Dir, undated; bell_brothers_249; shellac disc
  - Bach: Fantasia in C Major, Arthur Fiedler’s Sinfonietta, undated; bell_brothers_269; shellac disc
  - Bach: Fugue in D Minor (We All Believe in One God), E. Power Biggs, undated; bell_brothers_245; shellac disc
  - Bach: Sonata in E Major, Philadelphia Symphony Orchestra, 11/27/1939; bell_brothers_259; shellac disc
  - Bach: St. John’s Passion - All Is Fulfilled (Part 1), Marian Anderson, undated; bell_brothers_379; vitrolac disc
  - Bach: St. John’s Passion - All Is Fulfilled (Part 2), Marian Anderson, undated; bell_brothers_380; vitrolac disc
  - Ballad Hunter: Railroad Songs and Chisholm Trail, undated; bell_brothers_445; vinyl disc
  - Ballad Hunter: Sugarland, Texas; Jordan and Jubilee Songs from Livingston, Alabama, undated; bell_brothers_446; vinyl disc
  - Bañate en el Mar, undated; bell_brothers_199; shellac disc
  - Bandwagon, Dick Powell, Horace Heidt, Andy Devine; (No. 145); Lynn Murray, Stinko (No. 21), 03/18/1945; bell_brothers_610; vinyl disc
  - Basic Musical Library: John Charles Thomas (No. C-3 and C-4), undated; bell_brothers_489; vinyl disc
  - Basic Musical Library: Sons of the Pioneers (No. W-3 and W-4), undated; bell_brothers_531; vinyl disc
  - Basin Street (No. 51), 09/10/1944; bell_brothers_508; vinyl disc
  - Beethoven: Eroica Variations (Part 2) Claudio Arrau, undated; bell_brothers_226; shellac disc
  - Beethoven: Twelve Variations - Emanuel Feuermann (Part 1), 07/31/1939; bell_brothers_262; shellac disc
  - Beethoven: Twelve Variations - Emanuel Feuermann (Part 2), 07/31/1939; bell_brothers_258; shellac disc
  - Ben Bernie Program: Viennese Folk Song, Viola Philo, 08/24/1937; bell_brothers_203; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Bernard Rogers: Soliloquy for Flute and String, American Composers Orchestra, 04/29/1940; bell_brothers_389; vitrolac disc
  - Bing Crosby Outtakes: Wrap Your Troubles in Dreams; Blues Serenade, undated; bell_brothers_096; shellac disc
  - Bing Crosby, Bob Hope and Judy Garland, undated; bell_brothers_040; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Bing Crosby, Bob Hope and Judy Garland; Frank Sinatra, undated; bell_brothers_039; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Blockade, Walter Wagner, Twentieth Century Radio Production, (No. 1), undated; bell_brothers_442; vinyl disc
  - Bluebeard's Castle, Bartok, undated; bell_brothers_704; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Bob Burns, replacing Village Store (No. 62), 10/30/1944; bell_brothers_465; vinyl disc
  - Bob Hope (No. 13), undated; bell_brothers_504; vinyl disc
  - Bob Hope (No. 78), 10/24/1944; bell_brothers_513; vinyl disc
  - Bob Hope (No. 105), 05/01/1945; bell_brothers_519; vinyl disc
  - Boccherini: Sonata in A Major - Primrose and Kahn (Part 1), 07/24/1939; bell_brothers_260; shellac disc
  - Boccherini: Sonata in A Major - Primrose and Kahn (Part 2), 07/24/1939; bell_brothers_261; shellac disc
  - Boheme, English Libretto (Parts 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_734; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Boheme, English Libretto (Parts 3 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_735; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Boston Symphony Orchestra: Capriccio (Part 1), 03/19/1940; bell_brothers_228; shellac disc
  - Brahms: Sonata in F minor, Op. 120, No. 1 (Part 1) Mr. O’Connell, Primrose and Sanroma, 01/09/1939; bell_brothers_392; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Sonata in F minor, Op. 120, No. 1 (Part 2) Mr. O’Connell, Primrose and Sanroma, 01/09/1939; bell_brothers_393; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Sonata in F minor, Op. 120, No. 1 (Part 3) Mr. O’Connell, Primrose and Sanroma, 01/09/1939; bell_brothers_394; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Sonata in F minor, Op. 120, No. 1 (Part 4) Mr. O’Connell, Primrose and Sanroma, 01/09/1939; bell_brothers_395; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Sonata in F minor, Op. 120, No. 1 (Part 5) Mr. O’Connell, Primrose and Sanroma, 01/09/1939; bell_brothers_396; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Sonata in F minor, Op. 120, No. 1 (Part 6) Mr. O’Connell, Primrose and Sanroma, 01/09/1939; bell_brothers_397; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Tragic Overture, Op. 81, Toscanini and BBC Symphony Orchestra, (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_407; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Tragic Overture, Op. 81, Toscanini and BBC Symphony Orchestra, (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_408; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 1st Movement (Part 1), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_398; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 1st Movement (Part 2), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_399; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 1st Movement (Part 3), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_400; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 1st Movement (Part 4), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_401; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 1st Movement (Part 5), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_402; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 2nd Movement (Part 1), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_403; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 2nd Movement (Part 2), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_404; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 3rd Movement (Part 1), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_405; vitrolac disc
  - Brahms: Violin Concerto, 3rd Movement (Part 2), Jascha Heifetz and Boston Symphony Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_406; vitrolac disc
  - Bruckner: Symphony No. 7; Metropolitan Opera: Barbiere Di Siviglia, Act 2, 12/16/1950; bell_brothers_126; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Burns and Allen (No. 52), 10/17/1944; bell_brothers_460; vinyl disc
  - Burns and Allen (No. 53), 10/24/1944; bell_brothers_461; vinyl disc
  - Caravan, Jimmy Durante, Gary Moore (No. 24), undated; bell_brothers_606; vinyl disc
  - California Melodies (No. 56), 10/15/1944; bell_brothers_509; vinyl disc
  - Calypso; Bayon Songs, undated; bell_brothers_114; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Cardui, Announcements 1-6, undated; bell_brothers_790; vinyl disc
  - Cardui, Announcements 1-6, undated; bell_brothers_791; vinyl disc
  - Carlos Di Sarli: Tristeza Marina, tango; Anselmo Acuna El Resero, tango, undated; bell_brothers_097; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Chadwick: Quartet No. 8 (Parts 1 and 5), undated; bell_brothers_183; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Chadwick: Quartet No. 8 (Parts 2 and 6), undated; bell_brothers_184; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Chadwick: Quartet No. 8 (Parts 3 and 7), undated; bell_brothers_185; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Chadwick: Quartet No. 8 (Parts 4 and 8), undated; bell_brothers_186; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Chaliapin: Prisoner’s Song [sic], 01/04/1924; bell_brothers_263; shellac disc
  - "Chaliapin: She Laughed ", undated; bell_brothers_266; shellac disc
  - "Chaliapin: The Blind Ploughman ", 03/08/1927; bell_brothers_264; shellac disc
  - "Chaliapin: The Old Corporal ", undated; bell_brothers_265; shellac disc
  - Chant Of The Tobacco Auctioneer, Edwin C. Hill and The Famous Auctioneer, undated; bell_brothers_054; plastic disc
  - Chant Of The Tobacco Auctioneer, Edwin C. Hill and The Famous Auctioneer, undated; bell_brothers_055; plastic disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 1A-1B), undated; bell_brothers_033; shellac disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 2A-2B), undated; bell_brothers_022; shellac disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 3A-3B), undated; bell_brothers_034; shellac disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 4A), undated; bell_brothers_023; shellac disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 5A), undated; bell_brothers_018; shellac disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 7A-7B), undated; bell_brothers_013; shellac disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 9A-9B), undated; bell_brothers_024; shellac disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 11A-11B), undated; bell_brothers_031; shellac disc
  - Charles F. Lindsley (No. 13A-13B), undated; bell_brothers_030; shellac disc
  - Charlie McCarthy (No 78), 10/22/1944; bell_brothers_470; vinyl disc
  - Chausson: Songs of Love and Sea, Mona Paulee; CBS Symphony; Bernard Herrmann: Invitation to Music, 06/12/1946; bell_brothers_129; lacquer on glass disc
  - Comedy Caravan (No. 83), 01/26/1945; bell_brothers_471; vinyl disc
  - Comedy Caravan (No. 97), 05/04/1945; bell_brothers_473; vinyl disc
  - Command Performance (Unit 2), undated; bell_brothers_453; vinyl disc
  - Coronation of Queen Elizabeth (Part 1), 06/02/1953; bell_brothers_785; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Coronation of Queen Elizabeth (Part 2), 06/02/1953; bell_brothers_786; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Country Hoedown: Ernest Tubb, Master of Ceremonies, Faron Young, guest; (No. 7) Faron Young, Master of Ceremonies, Pee Wee King, guest (No. 8), undated; bell_brothers_634; vinyl disc
  - Country Hoedown: Faron Young, Master of Ceremonies, Patsy Cline, guest; (No. 45); Jimmy Dean, Master of Ceremonies, Eddie Arnold, guest (No. 46), undated; bell_brothers_636; vinyl disc
  - Country Hoedown: Jimmy Dean, Master of Ceremonies, Eddie Arnold, guest (No. 43); Eddie Arnold, Master of Ceremonies, George Morgan, guest (No. 44), undated; bell_brothers_635; vinyl disc
  - Courboin: Chorale No. 3 in A Minor, by Franc (Part 1), Mr. O'Connell [sic], 10/22/1939; bell_brothers_301; shellac disc
  - Courboin: Chorale No. 3 in A Minor, by Franck (Part 2), Mr. O'Connell [sic], 10/22/1939; bell_brothers_302; shellac disc
  - Courboin: Chorale No. 3 in A Minor, by Franck (Part 3), Mr. O'Connell [sic], 10/22/1939; bell_brothers_303; shellac disc
  - Courboin: Movement from Chorale No. 1 in E Major, by Franck, Mr. O'Connell [sic], undated; bell_brothers_304; shellac disc
  - Courboin: Pastorale, Op. 19, by Franck (Part 1), Mr. O'Connell [sic], 10/22/1939; bell_brothers_305; shellac disc
  - Courboin: Pastorale, Op. 19, by Franck (Part 2), Mr. O'Connell [sic], 10/22/1939; bell_brothers_306; shellac disc
  - Courboin: Pièce héroïque, by Franck (Part 1), Mr. Obonnell [sic], 10/22/1939; bell_brothers_307; shellac disc
  - Courboin: Pièce héroïque, by Franck (Part 2), Mr. O'Connell [sic], 10/22/1939; bell_brothers_308; shellac disc
  - Crankl, 3, undated; bell_brothers_068; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Crowd, undated; bell_brothers_080; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - D’Albert: Gavotte [sic] (Part 1), 08/13/1941; bell_brothers_166; lacquer on glass disc
  - D’Ambrosio: Quartet in C Minor, Op. 52 (Parts 1 and 3), 06/14/1938; bell_brothers_208; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - D’Ambrosio: Quartet in C Minor, Op. 52 (Parts 2 and 4), 06/14/1938; bell_brothers_209; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - D’Ambrosio: Quartet in C Minor, Op. 52 (Parts 5 and 7), 06/14/1938; bell_brothers_210; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - D’Ambrosio: Quartet in C Minor, Op. 52 (Parts 6 and 8), 06/14/1938; bell_brothers_211; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Dalabang Taga Bukid; Sa Punong Saguing, undated; bell_brothers_078; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - De Beriot: Violin Concerto, A Minor (Parts 1 and 3), undated; bell_brothers_153; lacquer on glass disc
  - De Falla: Hommage, J. M. Oyanguren, undated; bell_brothers_223; on shellac disc
  - Deems Taylor: Ramuncho, Introduction and Ballet (Part 2); Stoessel: Garrick (Part 4), undated; bell_brothers_158; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Deems Taylor: Ramuncho, Introduction and Ballet (Parts 1 and 3), undated; bell_brothers_157; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Delius; Metropolitan Opera: Barbiere Di Siviglia, Act 2, 12/16/1950; bell_brothers_127; lacquer on aluminum disc
  - Disabled American Veterans National Headquarters: Orrin Tucker and His Orchestra, undated; bell_brothers_690; vinyl disc
  - Dittersdorf: Quartet in E-flat Major (Part 1) Allegro (continued), Kreiner, undated; bell_brothers_321; vitrolac disc
  - Dittersdorf: Quartet in E-flat Major (Part 1) Allegro, Kreiner, undated; bell_brothers_320; vitrolac disc
  - Dittersdorf: Quartet in E-flat Major (Part 2) Minuetto, Kreiner, undated; bell_brothers_322; vitrolac disc
  - Dittersdorf: Quartet in E-flat Major (Part 3) Finale Allegro, Kreiner, undated; bell_brothers_323; vitrolac disc
  - Dohnanyi: Quintet No. 1, Op. 1, C Minor (Parts 1 and 3), 03/30/1943; bell_brothers_150; lacquer on glass disc
  - Dohnanyi: Quintet No. 1, Op. 1, C Minor (Parts 2 and 4), 03/30/1943; bell_brothers_151; lacquer on glass disc
  - Dohnanyi: Quintet No. 1, Op. 1, C Minor (Parts 5 and 6), 03/30/1943; bell_brothers_152; lacquer on glass disc
  - Downbeat, Percy Faith (Series H-7, No. 126), undated; bell_brothers_612; vinyl disc
  - Duffy's Tavern (No. 18), 04/18/1944; bell_brothers_457; vinyl disc
  - Duffy's Tavern (No. 4, Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_689; vinyl disc
  - Duffy's Tavern replaced by Fanny Brice (No. 92), 04/29/1945; bell_brothers_515; vinyl disc
  - Duke, undated; bell_brothers_103; lacquer on glass disc
  - Dvorak: Quartet in F Major, 1st Movement, Budapest String Quartet (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_368; vitrolac disc
  - Dvorak: Quartet in F Major, 1st Movement, Budapest String Quartet (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_369; vitrolac disc
  - Dvorak: Quartet in F Major, 3rd Movement, Budapest String Quartet, undated; bell_brothers_370; vitrolac disc
  - Dvorak: Quartet in F Major, 4th Movement, Budapest String Quartet, undated; bell_brothers_371; vitrolac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 2), undated; bell_brothers_021; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 3), undated; "bell_brothers_027 "; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 4), undated; bell_brothers_020; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 7), undated; bell_brothers_017; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 8), undated; bell_brothers_019; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 9), undated; bell_brothers_009; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O' Riley (No. 10), undated; bell_brothers_008; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 11), undated; bell_brothers_007; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 12), undated; bell_brothers_011; shellac disc
  - Edmund Breese in Memories; Life O’ Riley (No. 13), undated; bell_brothers_029; shellac disc
  - Elsie Houston: Seren Popular, Spanish Songs [sic] (No. 1-4), undated; bell_brothers_428; shellac disc
  - Elsie Houston: Seren Popular, Spanish Songs [sic], (No. 5-7), undated; bell_brothers_429; shellac disc
  - Evil Old Nightmare; The Yao Yao Girl, undated; bell_brothers_219; shellac disc
  - Eyes Wright, Martha Wright with The Page Cavanaugh Trio and Mel Allen; (No. 7-8), undated; bell_brothers_579; vinyl disc
  - Ezio Pinza: Caro Mio Ben, by Giordani; O Bellissimi Capelli, by Falconieri, undated; bell_brothers_298; shellac disc
  - Ezio Pinza: Oblivion Soave, by Monteverdi; Donzelle Fuggite, by Cavalli, undated; bell_brothers_299; shellac disc
  - Fantasia on a Theme by Thomas Tallis (Part 1), undated; bell_brothers_419; shellac disc
  - Fantasia on a Theme by Thomas Tallis (Part 2), undated; bell_brothers_420; shellac disc
  - Fantasia on a Theme by Thomas Tallis (Part 3), undated; bell_brothers_421; shellac disc
  - Fantasia on a Theme by Thomas Tallis (Part 4), undated; bell_brothers_422; shellac disc
  - Faure: La Bonne Chanson, Op. 61, (Parts 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_342; vitrolac disc
  - Faure: La Bonne Chanson, Op. 61, (Parts 3 and 4), undated; bell_brothers_343; vitrolac disc
  - Faure: La Bonne Chanson, Op. 61, (Parts 7 and 8), undated; bell_brothers_346; vitrolac disc
  - Faure: La Bonne Chanson, Op. 61, (Part 5), undated; bell_brothers_344; vitrolac disc
  - Faure: La Bonne Chanson, Op. 61, (Part 6), undated; bell_brothers_345; vitrolac disc
  - Faure: La Bonne Chanson, Op. 61, (Part 9), undated; bell_brothers_347; vitrolac disc
  - Fauré: Le Secret - Nell (noure), undated; bell_brothers_227; shellac disc
  - Faure: Panzéra, (baritone), Panzéra-Baillot, (piano), (disc 1 of 2), undated; bell_brothers_348; vitrolac disc
  - Faure: Panzéra, (baritone), Panzéra-Baillot, (piano), (disc 2 of 2), undated; bell_brothers_349; vitrolac disc
  - Fibber McGee (No. 74), 10/10/1944; bell_brothers_468; vinyl disc
  - Fibber McGee (No. 75), 10/17/1944; bell_brothers_469; vinyl disc
  - Fletcher v. Fletcher, 07/13/1946; bell_brothers_144; lacquer on glass disc
  - Ford Dealers of America, Special New Car Announcement, (No. 1 and 2), undated; bell_brothers_447; vinyl disc
  - Ford Dealers of America, Special New Car Announcement, (No. 1), undated; bell_brothers_450; vinyl disc
  - Ford Star Jubilee, 09/24/1955; bell_brothers_004; acetate on aluminum disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 89-90), undated; bell_brothers_568; vinyl disc
  - Forward March featuring The U. S. Army Band Orchestra Conducted by Major Hugh Curry and The Army Band Chorus with Solo Vocalists (No. 123-124), undated; bell_brothers_569; vinyl disc